# **BRAD DEIBERT**

+1(406) 885-0447  $\diamond$  Missoula, MT

bradeibert7@gmail.com LinkedIn Personal Website

### **OBJECTIVE**

Productive, team-oriented Software Engineer with 3 years of professional full stack software development experience. Interested in full-time front-end, full stack, or back-end engineering roles. I prefer a hybrid work environment, even though I typically try to work in office 5 days a week. I will consider remote for the right position.

#### **SKILLS**

**Technical:** API/services development (.NET, Flask), React/Redux, SQL and NoSQL databases (PostgreSQL, Azure CosmosDB), infrastructure as code (Terraform), Javascript, HTML, CSS

Non-technical: Product ownership and leadership, communication and collaboration, Agile development

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Engineer II

Submittable

Jun 2021 - Present Missoula, MT

- Designed and built a bulk data ingestion process (ETL) from scratch. In use today for managing the ingestion of millions of records of Organization data into a NoSQL database. **Tech:** .**NET Console application, Azure CosmosDB, Azure Blob Storage**
- Primary tech lead/service owner of an internal service that provides an API to query/access the Organizations data mentioned above. **Tech: .NET Web API, Azure CosmosDB**
- Lone front-end engineer on a new greenfield software product at inception. Developed the product until our first sale, team size grew from 2 to 12 at its peak. Tech: Next.js/React, .NET Web API, PostgreSQL

# Software Engineer Intern

onX Maps

May 2020 - Aug 2020 Missoula, MT

- Shipped contributions to a public facing SPA application (onX's website), and an internal API. **Tech: Vue.js**, **Flask API**
- Demo new development to stakeholders

### **EDUCATION**

## B.S. in Computer Science, University of Montana

2019 - 2021

Minor in Mathematics

Graduated Magna Cum Laude (3.74 GPA)

### A.S. in General Studies, Flathead Valley Community College

Honors Program Student

2016 - 2018

### **AWARDS**

• 2021 President's Outstanding Senior, Computer Science (University of Montana)

Awarded to one senior from each academic department. Winners selected on "the basis of academic performance in addition to devotion to the excellence of their departments and The University of Montana".

#### **PROJECTS**

**Fuelcast.net** As the CS senior capstone experience at the University of Montana, I lead a small team of my peers to assist a real world client's development for an existing web application. My team gathered requirements, created specification documents, and implemented solutions to satisfy client needs. One teammate and I each received a job offer after the class. Fuelcast.net site